So before we're going to attach the front to the rest of the pieces, what we're going to do is take some elastic and we're actually going to make a little holder to hold bottles of wine.
So this will make it so easy if you're going grocery shopping and have a few bottles so they don't slide around.
Also if you're going on a picnic if you don't drink of course, you can just add some bottle of water or ice tea or something like that.
So what I did was just take a piece of elastic and your just going to measure out the same size as your bag.
You want to leave about three inches on either side and just go ahead and cut, your going to find your center point put a pin and take two more pins.
I'm just going to give about two fingers worth ease because what you want theoretically is for this to be able to stretch and securely hold your wine bottles.
So two fingers of ease would be great.
Then you're going to put a pin on each side again just put your two fingers, then you can trim some of the excess.
You do want to leave a little bit of excess into the seam allowance cause this will just make sure that once you stitch everything up that your wine holder is secured.
So go ahead and take it to your machine we're just going to run two stitches on either side and then a stitch down the center.
You want to go back and forth a few times just to make sure that's pretty secured. Go ahead and do the center seam the same way again I like to make these fairly large because if you do want to say use one of those two litter bottles of water or I think a liter in a half, those are fairly large cause you do want to give space for them to fairly fit.
Then do your last seam and now you are ready to pin it to the rest of your lining pieces.